minister of works and transport Rohan
senen believes that personal
responsibility is 90 of the challenge as
it relates to Road Safety addressing
recipients of arrival lives road safety
awards Minister synonym said the
ministry will continue to do its part to
ensure the safety of citizens on the
nation's roadways I urge you all do your
job
let us get back that personal
responsibility back into the hands of
the drivers letting them know that if
they breached
the rules and the regulations that there
are penalties because once we know there
are penalties then we think twice about
what we're doing and you have the
support from the ministry on that
Personnel from the fire service Global
Medical Response TNT traffic wardens
transits and Municipal Police were
acknowledged for their service they were
awarded in categories such as leadership
and excellence in route safety Woodside
energy has sponsored the event for the
past nine years country manager Juan
Vasquez said the company has decided to
take a leading role in promoting route
safety and will dedicate time and
resources he reiterated that team effort
is needed to achieve the school every
interaction that you have every time you
stop someone every time you curve a
behavior
as much as that person may be vexed as
people say here right because they
there's they're stopped you have saved
someone's life presidents of arrive
alive Sharon inglefield said the
National Road Safety Council has
developed a plan for road safety by
identifying short medium and long-term
priorities for action one of these
includes a Safe Systems approach for
road safety the safe system approach
anticipates
and accommodates for human error
it incorporates Road and vehicle designs
that limit the force of crashes to
levels that are within human tolerance
to prevent death and serious injuries
she said it is imperative that the plan
is approved by government adequate
funding is provided and strict timelines
are met Kimberly de Souza tdt news